articopia.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Articopia.com

## Privacy Policy

**Registration Forms**  

Our site's registration form and account management form require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their birthdate). Contact information from the registration forms is used to send information about our company, and to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Pictures/Avatars uploaded by users are used purely to personalize the website and the articles. They are not shared with any outside party.

Demographic and profile data are also collected at our site. We use these data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

**Automatic Information Collection**

We use your IP address, browser type, domain names, and access times, operating system, country of origin, page views, and users sessions to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP, browser type, etc. are used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site uses cookies (a piece of data stored on a user's computer) to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit. Or, it may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences.

**External Sites and Advertisements**

This site contains links to other sites. Articopia.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Artiopia.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

**Sharing Information**

Articopia.com does not share, sell or rent your email addresses to outside third parties. Personally identifiable information will only be disclosed due to law or court demands (see our legal disclaimer below for more information)

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include password protected directories through the use of .htaccess files and customized cgi programs to prevent access to specific areas of the web site.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact: admin[at]articopia.com.
